http://www.svretirement.org/privacy-policy

LifestylesDecision GuideSenior LivingAssisted LivingFloor PlansAmenitiesCommunity FeaturesApartment AmenitiesActivities & WellnessTrue Restaurant DiningUpcoming EventsGalleryAboutAbout UsCareersResourcesPlanning ToolsLong-Term Care InsuranceVeterans BenefitsBlogContactClick to call our front deskContact usLifestylesDecision GuideIndependent & Residential LivingAssisted LivingFloor PlansAmenitiesCommunity FeaturesApartment AmenitiesActivities & WellnessTrue Restaurant DiningGalleryAboutAbout UsCareersResourcesPlanning ToolsLong-Term Care InsuranceVeterans BenefitsBlogLifestylesDecision GuideIndependent & Residential LivingAssisted LivingFloor PlansAmenitiesCommunity FeaturesApartment AmenitiesActivities & WellnessTrue Restaurant DiningGalleryAboutAbout UsCareersResourcesPlanning ToolsLong-Term Care InsuranceVeterans BenefitsBlogContactPrivacy PolicyView our policy regarding any personal information you may supply to us when visiting svliving.org.Privacy PolicyUpdated December 1, 2016Hughson Samaritan Village owns
and operates http://www.svliving.org (the
“Site”). This page informs you of our
policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information
we receive from users of the Site.We use your personal information
only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the
collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. If you do not
agree with our policies and practices, your only recourse is not to use our
website.Information Collection and UseWhile using our Site, we may ask
you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be
used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may
include, but is not limited to, your name, address, email address, and telephone
number (“Personal Information”). We may also collect information about you that
individually does not identify you such as your age, gender, and interests; how
you came to the website (e.g., search engine, third-party website, media
campaign or email); and features of the website you use. Log DataLike many site operators, we
collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log
Data”). This Log Data may include
information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser
type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date
of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics. This
information is statistical data and does not identify any individual. It helps
us to improve our Site and deliver better and more personalized future
services.  We do not collect personal
information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal
information about you that we collect from other sources or that you provide to
us. Cookies (or browser cookies) are
a string of information that a Site stores on a visitor’s computer, and, that
the visitor’s browser provides to the Site each time the visitor returns.  If you do not wish to have cookies placed on
your computer, you may set your browser to refuse cookies before using this
Site.  Refusing cookies may affect the
proper function of certain features of the Site. How We Use Your DataThe information we collect about
you or that you provide to us, including personal information, may be used by
us to provide you with information, products, or services that you request from
us, for marketing purposes, to allow you to participate in interactive features
on our Site, in any other way we may describe when you provide the information,
or for any other purpose with your consent.
We never sell your personal information.Tracking Technologies and AdvertisingOur Site uses Google Analytics to
track Site activity and visitor behavior.
You may opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics by using the Google
Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on (https://tools.google.com/dlpage.gaoptout/). Data SecurityThe security of your Personal
Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission
over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we
strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal
Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Changes to This Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy is effective
as of December 1, 2016 and will remain in effect except with respect to any
changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately
after being posted on this page.We reserve the right to update or
change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy
periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications
to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgement of the
modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy
Policy.If we make any material changes
to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you
have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our Site.EnforcementsIf you feel this Site is not
following its stated Privacy Policy, you may contact us at 7700 Fox Road, Hughson,
CA 95326 or phone number 209-883-3000, state or local chapters of the Better
Business Bureau.Contact UsIf you have any questions about
this Privacy Policy, please contact us. We’re here to help!Have a question? Eager to tour? Fill out the form below and we'll be in touch with you shortly.I am interested in... (Select one)Independent LivingResidential LivingAssisted LivingI would like to receive occasional email updates from Samaritan Village.Thank you! Your submission has been received!Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the formCall today! 209-883-30007700 Fox Road, Hughson, CA 95326RCFE #507002396LifestylesDecision GuideSenior LivingAssisted LivingFloor PlansCommunityAmenitiesActivitiesGalleryAbout UsUpcoming EventsResourcesPlanning ToolsLong-Term CareVeterans BenefitsBlogCareersSamaritan Village is a not-for-profit organization, empowering seniors to maintain a superior quality of life through our Senior Living and Assisted Living retirement lifestyle options.Copyright 2020 Samaritan Village  |  All Rights Reserved  |  Privacy Policy  |  Resident Confidentiality  |  COVID-19
